[change location](https://aerobasegroup.com/locality/)   321-802-5889      321-733-7477

* 
* Search

* Menu  
    * Parts Lookup  

* Our Story  
* Parts  
    * Parts Lookup  

* Privacy Policy  

Privacy Policy AeroBase Group Privacy Policy
============================================

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which AeroBase Group collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the aerobasegroup.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by AeroBase Group.

**

ITAR Controlled Items

**

AeroBase Group may be required to notify the US Department of State, the US Department of Commerce, or other government entities in instances where ITAR controlled items are being sold or exported. AeroBase Group does abide by all applicable US export controls laws and regulation and may be called upon by the US Government to provide information on request originating from Banned Countries or Entities as defined by the US Department of Commerce, US Department of State, and Homeland Security.

**

Personal identification information

**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**

Non-personal identification information

**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**

Web browser cookies

**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**

How we use collected information

**

AeroBase Group may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

* To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
* To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
* To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
* To process payments: We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
* To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature: To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
* To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**

How we protect your information

**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**

Sharing your personal information

**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**

Third party websites

**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**

Changes to this privacy policy

**

AeroBase Group has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**

Your acceptance of these terms

**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**

Contacting us

**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
AeroBase Group  
www.aerobasegroup.com  
Contact@AeroBaseGroup.com  
  
This document was last updated on January 1, 2014

* Recent:

* 
* ISO 9001:2015 + AS9120B Phone: 1 (321) 802-5889  
    Fax: 1 (321) 733-7477
    
    3555 Agricultural Center Dr.  
    St. Augustine, FL  32092

* **Company**

* **Resources**

* **Parts**

#### Defense News

* [Here are the munitions Navy jets used for first time against Houthis](https://www.defensenews.com/news/your-navy/2024/07/25/here-are-the-munitions-navy-jets-used-for-first-time-against-houthis/)  
    07/25/24 12:32pm  
    
    An F/A-18E Super Hornet fighter jet prepares to take off from the flight deck of the aircraft carrier Dwight D. Eisenhower in January in the Red Sea. (Mass Communication Specialist 3rd Class Janae Chambers/Navy)
    
* [B-1 bomber crash report blasts crew mistakes, culture of ‘complacency’](https://www.defensenews.com/air/2024/07/25/b-1-bomber-crash-report-blasts-crew-mistakes-culture-of-complacency/)  
    07/25/24 12:00pm  
    
    A B-1B Lancer bomber that crashed while landing at Ellsworth Air Force Base, South Dakota, on Jan. 4, 2024, skidded 5,000 feet and then erupted into flames. The nearly $451 million bomber was a total loss. (Air Force)
    
* [Dassault says Rafale jet production ramp-up hit by supply chain snags](https://www.defensenews.com/global/europe/2024/07/24/dassault-says-rafale-jet-production-ramp-up-hit-by-supply-chain-snags/)  
    07/24/24 09:57am  
    
    French President Emmanuel Macron speaks with Dassault Aviation's CEO Eric Trappier (2nd L), in front of a model of the French multirole fighter aircraft Dassault Rafale as he visits the International Paris Air Show at the Paris Le Bourget Airport on June 19, 2023. (Photo by Ludovic Marin/POOL/AFP via Getty Images)
    
* [Boeing says it will shun fixed-price contracts for drone wingmen](https://www.defensenews.com/air/2024/07/23/boeing-says-it-will-shun-fixed-price-contracts-for-drone-wingmen/)  
    07/23/24 12:29pm  
    
    The Royal Australian Air Force has experimented with teaming drones up with piloted aircraft through its Loyal Wingman program, which uses Boeing's MQ-28 Ghost Bat. The U.S. Air Force is interested in Australia's experiments with the Ghost Bat as it considers how its own program will take shape. (Boeing Australia)

Recent parts by keyword  

The AeroBase Group Family ..

* Simplified purchasing with an easy to use e-commerce platform.

* Commercial and industrial medical products and supplies.

* National stock number distribution and purchasing services.

© Copyright 2024 AeroBase Group, Inc. | Cage: 74B05

All product and company names are trademarks ™ or registered ® trademarks of their respective holders. Use of them does not imply any affiliation with or endorsement by them.

v5.3.0

##### Compare Now »

Clear | Hide

* (choose another nsn)
* (choose another nsn)
* (choose another nsn)
* (choose another nsn)
